[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is my desktop's CPU brand?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "INTEL"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What crashes when I open 46 tabs?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "WINDOWS"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What browser do We open only to download Chrome?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _",
    "answer": "EDGE"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Where does dust go to start a new civilization?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _",
    "answer": "CASE"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What steals RAM like a crypto miner?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "CHROME"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What do We never clean until it stops working or get noisy?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _",
    "answer": "FANS"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What must a screen have according to you?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "SPEAKERS"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What mode does your PC enter when you're idle for too long?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "SLEEP"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What connector do I flip 3 times before it plugs?",
    "preview": "_  _  _",
    "answer": "USB"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What do We blame when lag ruins my game?",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _",
    "answer": "WIFI"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Youâ€™ve completed all questions! Time to reveal the answer.",
    "preview": "_  _  _  _  _   _  _  _  _  _   _  _   _  _  _  _",
    "answer": "CHECK UNDER MY DESK"
  }
]
